A camera
In this room
Why is this here
Your parents put it here
They and Daniel
put on a sob story together
just to make me drop my guard
Did you get the formula
No
Find a way
to destroy the feed he mixed
and force him to remix it
Then put the camera
in the mixing room secretly
As for what happens next
you don't need to worry
How could they do this
I'm their child too
Did they even think about me
Don't cry
You still have me
My heart is truly broken this time
Since they'll do anything
for Daniel
they can rely on him for retirement
I'll only do my basic duty to them
Lewes
You knew their plan
and you're still mixing feed
You're beating them at their own game
You know me best, honey
If Zoe
really uses this formula for production
her factory
is doomed to fail